Hey there!
Whether you're a solo developer or running
a tech team of 50 people,
you've probably faced the same AI challenge:
scattered tools and rising costs.
Your team uses ChatGPT for one thing,
Claude for another, local models for privacy,
and suddenly you've lost track of who's
spending what on which AI service.
No usage insights, no centralized control.
That's exactly why we built Bodhi App.
Bodhi App is your complete AI stack -
whether you're a team of one or one hundred.
Run it locally on your laptop,
deploy it on your company network,
or spin it up as a Docker service.
Local models for privacy, remote APIs
with your own keys for power,
role-based access for your team,
and complete usage visibility.
Plus, we're building in MCP support
for centralized agentic workflows -
so your AI agents can discover and connect
to tools automatically.
One platform, all your AI needs covered.
We'll be at AI Agentic Summit Bangalore
on July 2nd - come see us in action!
Bring your AI chaos,
we'll show you how to organize it.